Another big problem in the speech analytics space, when customers first bring the software on is that they they are blown away by the fact that an engine can monitor 100 of KPIs.
Right?
everything from minute compliance issues to, you know, human, human interaction, empathy measurements, to upsell aptitudes to closing aptitudes.
there are hundreds, literally, of KPIs that one could look at.
and the speech analytics companies have typically gone to the customer and really bang that drum.
Look at all of these things that we're gonna help you keep an eye on.
the reality, however, is that a company, even a contact center manager, they can't keep track in their brain, even if they have a report in front of them.
of that many KPIs.
Mhmm.
And frankly, it's overwhelming.
So what successful companies do is they bite off no more than they chew at any given time.
The reality is is you can only train a call center agent on a maximum of 3 skills at any given day.
Right?
And by focusing on, focusing on problem areas, for a week, for a month, depending on how bad things are.
and then once you've mastered that skill, take a baseline of of your performance and move on to the next worst skill, right, is the way that companies succeed using this product.